Lili J. Begum

TECHNOLOGY STRATEGY & TRANSFORMATION SPECIALIST



07517 777768 || 📧 LIL.IMIJ1@GMAIL.COM || ከ @LILIJ





PROFILE ||

Experienced in growth strategy and consulting. My current focus is on global transformation, analytics, and product management. I embrace change and am all about innovation and future proofing. I am grateful to have worked in multiple roles which have given me the opportunity to up-skill myself, build an amazing network and expand my knowledge to further discover my strength areas as well as show others the difference they can make. I am a strong advocate for inclusion and encouraging growth and I am never not learning something new.

KEY PROJECTS ||

I created a suite of workforce management tools for commercial delivery & insight, ensuring seamless execution of critical business processes, allowing the business to execute top priority initiatives. A recent example involves analysis of 2 million hours (over 800k individual time entries) in under 2 minutes, resulting in cost savings of at least £20,000 a month per business unit.

I recently ran a workshop in Belgium as part of a "Digitisation of Global Mobility" series to highlight the importance of tech and how we can utilise various tools to make our work more efficient. My session received the most positive feedback with requests to learn more which has led to more client wins for the company and our Belgian colleagues.

KEY SKILLS ||

- Product Management and being the "go to"
- Agile Management
 - o Azure DevOps, Kanban
- Business Intelligence & Analytics
 - o Excel, Alteryx
- Data Visualisation
 - o Power Bi (Power Query, DAX), Tableau
- **Robotic Process Automation**
 - o UiPath, Postman
- Microsoft 365, Power Apps, SQL server
- **Google Suite**

- Client Demonstrations, Workshops
- Pitching, Sales, Consulting
- RFPs / Proposals
- **Process Mapping:**
 - o Visio
- Manage stakeholder expectations
- Produce comprehensive documentation
- Clear communication
- User Experience (UX)
- **Version Control**

WORK EXPERIENCE | |

GLOBAL TRANSFORMATION SPECIALIST & PRODUCT MANAGER

VIALTO PARTNERS, LONDON: MAY 2022 - PRESENT

(Part of the PwC business unit acquired by CD&R) My role involves partnering with leadership to contribute to strategic projects.

- Developing deeper understanding of key value drivers,
- Identifying opportunities, cost savings and improvement areas.
- Providing levels of visibility and forecasting available for the first time, becoming a trusted advisor.
- Managing a portfolio of projects to drive adoption of tech platforms.

- Working in an agile way and building strong relationships with key stakeholders.
- Providing insightful demos and workshops as well as supporting onboarding.
- Assisting with user stories, testing and availability of applications, ensuring best practice
- Leveraging complex data, creating in-depth analyses, transformed into easy to read, visual data.
- Acting as connection across multiple lines of service, working with wider teams to provide input and get feedback to further develop solutions and platform.
- Identifying product gaps and shaping global product roadmaps.
- Producing project plans, communication plans and reference materials to keep teams on track, users up to date, and upskill the workforce.

TAX TRANSFORMATION SPECIALIST

PWC, LONDON: JAN 2016 - MAY 2022

- Working at a Big 4 in a split role across tax, technology, and managed services
- Leading and Managing client engagements, being the main day to day contact.
- Creating significant financial efficiencies.
- Managing junior members of staff.
- Hand selected for an operations tech secondment when there was a high demand.
- Global co-ordination, working closely with overseas offices and territories

SENIOR MORTGAGE CONSULTANT

COUNTRYWIDE, LONDON & SOUTHWEST: FEB 2014 – JAN 2016

- Working at the UK's largest property services group, adapting to a heavily regulated market and keeping up to date with relevant financial changes that may affect business
- High pressure role where I regularly exceeded targets and managed budgets as well as analysing risks

Roles prior to 2014 available upon request.

QUALIFICATIONS ||

IN PROGRESS 2022 - 2023

Microsoft PL900, Google Cloud Practitioner (GCP), Alteryx Advanced

POST UNIVERSITY CERTIFICATIONS

2014 - 2021

- Alteryx Core (Jan 2021)
- ATT (Nov 2020 May 2021)
- Kubicle, Analysing & Visualising Data with Power Bi (May 2020)
- Udacity, Business Analyst Nanodegree (Feb 2020)
- IFS, CeMap (May 2014)

KINGSTON UNIVERSITY, BA (HONS)

2010-2013

Marketing Communications & Advertising (1st)

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS | |

- Gym & Aerial
- Sports (Rugby, Football, F1, Tennis)

- Creative (Art, Writing, Videography & Photography)
- Coding (as well as low / no code platforms)

REFERENCES | |

Available upon request